{
    "question": "1.what dion east?    A.mie ayam \r\nB.fred rice\r\nC.Bakso \r\nD.Bakmi\r\n\r\n2.what dion Drinks?\r\nA.orenge juice \r\nB.Milk\r\nC.water \r\nD.Mango juice \r\n\r\n3.dion has lunch at...\r\nA.Restaurant\r\nB.kitchen\r\nC.Canteen\r\n\r\n4.we have.....in the morning\r\nA.breakfast\r\nB.lunch\r\nC.dinner\r\nd.eat\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. B.fred rice</p><p>2. D.Mango juice </p><p>3. C.dinner</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>I hope it helps, don&#039;t forget to follow my ig, I&#039;ll follow back</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "ana-and-anto-smart-students-a-is-b-am-c-are-d-was-710",
            "question": "Ana and Anto . . . smart students.\r\nA. is\r\nB. am\r\nc. are\r\nd. was\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C. are</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>karena Ana dan Anto adalah 2 orang atau lebih</p><p>dari satu karena itu harus menggunakan are</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu semangat terus!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-bantu-buatin-pantun-nasehat-pakai-bahasa-palembang-pliss-190",
            "question": "Tolong bantu buatin pantun nasehat pakai bahasa Palembang pliss\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>di kanan ada tembok batu</p><p>di kiri ada pagar besar</p><p>kalo mau juara  satu </p><p>tentu harus giat belajar </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>MAAF KALO SALAH #wibu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "binder-note-high-a-penguin-is-aquatic-flightless-bird-most-of-t-674",
            "question": "Binder Note High a    Penguin is aquatic, flightless bird. Most of their species live in cold climates area. They have\r\nadapted to live in cold climates.\r\nPenguins have to keep body temperatures high to remain active. They have thick skin and lots of\r\nfat (blubber) under their skin to keep warm in cold weather.\r\nThey also huddle together with their friends to keep warm. Emperor penguins have developed a\r\nsocial behavior that when it gets cold, they huddle together in groups that may comprise several\r\nthousand penguins.\r\nThe dark colored feathers of a penguin's back surface absorb heat from the sun. It also keeps\r\nthem to warm up too.\r\nPenguins tightly packed feathers overlap to provide waterproofing and warmth. They coat their\r\nfeathers with oil from a gland near the tail to increase impermeability. Waterproofing is critical to\r\n5. From the text we know that...\r\nA. penguin fats help them absorb the heat from sun\r\nB. penguins huddle together during mating season\r\nC. penguins can swim faster by coating their feather with oil\r\nD. penguin fats protect them from cold\r\nE. penguins' beaks are waterproof\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. penguin fats protect them from cold</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jawaban-soal-vocabulary-building-kelas-11-259",
            "question": "Jawaban soal vocabulary building kelas 11\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>halaman brp y??</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>........</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "we-go-to-the-beach-two-week-ago-321",
            "question": "We (go) to the beach two week ago\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>we went to the beach two weeks ago</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>past tense jd v2</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>We <strong><em>went</em></strong> to the beach two weeks ago</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong><em>Past tense</em></strong> merupakan kata yang digunakan untuk menjelaskan kejadian yang telah terjadi di masa lampau.</p><p>Perbedaannya dengan <em>present tense </em>adalah <strong><em>verb</em></strong> yang digunakan.</p><p><em>Present tense</em> menggunakan <strong><u>verb 1</u></strong>, dan <em>past tense</em> menggunakan <strong><u>verb 2</u></strong>.</p><p></p><p>Maka verb 2 dari go adalah:</p><p>go \u2192 went</p><p></p><p>Past Tense Sentences:</p><h2><strong><u>We </u></strong><strong><u>went</u></strong><strong><u> to the beach two weeks ago</u></strong></h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "4-the-best-arrangement-of-these-jumbled-sentences-to-be-a-good-r-109",
            "question": "4. The best arrangement of these jumbled sentences to be a good recount text is....    a. Finally I went home with my friends happily.\r\nb.After swimming, I put on again my bathing suit and go to the bathroom to rinse my body.\r\nc. Yesterday I went to swimming pool with my friends.\r\nd.I brought my bag which is full of things I needed in the swimming pool.\r\ne.I wore my clothes and put all the wet clothes into the plastic bag, so my bag would not get wet by water.\r\nf. When we arrived there, I changed my clothes into swimsuit then I did a little warming up before I got into the pool.\r\nA. C-d-f-e-b-a\r\nB. a-c-b-d-f-e\r\nC. d-c-b-f-a-e-\r\nD. b-d-a-f-e-\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>c-d-f-b-e-a</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: i can&#039;t find any correct answer from the option. so, i make one of mine. hope this find you helpful ^\u2022^</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-would-you-mind-not-closing-the-window-the-sentence-has-the-615",
            "question": "6. \"Would you mind not closing the window?\"    The sentence has the same meaning with :\r\nA. Do not close the window, please.\r\nB. Close the window, please,\r\nC. The window must be closed\r\nD. Don't open the window, please.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Do not close the window, please.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-what-do-you-use-the-plate-for-answer-2-where-does-a-pol-297",
            "question": "1. What do you use the plate for?    Answer:....\r\n2. Where does a policeman work?\r\nAnswer:...\r\n3. What is the activity of a butterfly?\r\nAnswer:....\r\n4. What is the activity of a pilot?\r\nAnswer:\r\n5. Where does a waiter work?\r\nAnswer:.....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>1. we use the plate to eat/to put our food on it.</p><p>2. policeman works in the police station.</p><p>3. flying around from one flower to another flowers.</p><p>4. pilot is someone who fly an aeroplane.</p><p>5. the waiter works in a restaurant.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "my-uncle-loves-to-tell-jokes-to-make-us-laugh-he-is-380",
            "question": "My uncle loves to tell jokes to make us laugh he is\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>comedian</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu,boleh bantu follow nya ga? engga maksa kok hehe ^_^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "salah-satu-permainan-tradisional-780",
            "question": "Salah satu permainan tradisional\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>egrang, congklak</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>petak umpet,bola bekel, gundu,tali karet</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}